drivers-applications.com 2010-04-02

# Privacy Policy

Drivers-Applications.com Privacy Policy

Last updated: 10th April 2009

As a fellow Internet user myself, I totally respect your online privacy. So it goes without saying that I'm fully committed to safeguarding your online privacy while you're here at the Drivers-Applications

And that's precisely why I've decided to include the following, which discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. You can read it below!

Log Files

Like most standard websites, this website uses log files. These include: Internet Protocol addresses (IP addresses), browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Web Cookies

Web cookies (also known as HTTP cookies, or just cookies) are parcels of text that are sent by a server to a Web browser, and then sent back unchanged by the browser each time it accesses that server. In other words, a cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s computer that is tied to information about the user.

  *  **Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.**
  *  **Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.**
  *  **Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the**[Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com.pk/url?q=http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html&ei=BwFaS97oEtjPjAe62KigAg&sa=X&oi=nshc&resnum=1&ct=result&cd=1&ved=0CAsQzgQoAA&usg=AFQjCNErzzQyCWbNaGZNGinPFOa1jyNkiQ).  

Links

This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. I encourage you, when you leave this website, to read the privacy statements/policies of each and every website you visit, as this particular privacy policy applies solely to this particular website.

Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

I currently work with Google Adsense. If you have any questions, please check [Google Adsense's ](http://adsense.google.com/)websites for their respective privacy policies.

Webmaster Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding the Drivers-Applications.com, Please [contact us](http://www.drivers-applications.com/2009/01/contact-us.html).[ ](http://drivers-applications.blogspot.com/)
